(Sheldon:)More?
(Leonard:)I'm afraid so.
(Leonard:)You know the cashew chicken
I get you on Monday nights?
Yes, from Szechwan Palace.
Szechwan Palace closed two years ago.
(Penny:)What?
- Where did my cashew chicken come from?
- Golden Dragon.
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)No, this isn't right.
No, our food always comes
in Szechwan Palace containers.
(Leonard:)Yeah, well, before they went out of
business, I bought 4000 containers.
(Leonard:)I keep them in the trunk of my car.
(Howard:)But...
(Sheldon:)Oh, this changes everything.
(Leonard:)I thought that might take
his mind off the cushion.
(Sheldon:)What's real? What isn't?
How can I know?
- You did make that up, right?
- Oh, God, I wish I had.